[{"answer": "The whole pla", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " You've read every play by my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Now don't get upset. Daddy, but there's this boy... and I think he might ask..", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What if she never starts dating", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "So he has this huge raging fit about my friend and insists that I go to his mal", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend didn't even go to high schoo", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Then tell them I had a seizure", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I thought you were punishing me", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "A hundred bucks a date", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Forget her sister, then", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What plan", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What is it with this chick?  She have three tits", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That's where we can help you.  With my friend", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend, my friend, you're not looking at the big picture.  my friend's just a pawn. We set this whole thing up so my friend can get the girl", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Oh, I thought you might have a date  I don't know why I'm bothering to ask, but are you going to my friend's party Saturday night", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I think you're a freak.  I think you do this to torture me.  And I think you suck", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Daddy, I", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "If you must know, we were attempting to go to a small study group of friends", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend, I don't think the highlights of dating my friend are going to include doo", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "All I know is", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You're not okay", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Uh, uh. You lie down and you'll go to slee", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I told yo", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Sure, I d", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You went to the party?  I thought we were officially opposed to suburban social activity", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You didn't have a choice?  Where's my friend and what have you done with her", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I didn't have a choice", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I did my friend a favor and it backfired", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You didn't have a choice?  Where's my friend and what have you done with her", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You didn'", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Unwelcome?  I guess someone still has her panties in a twist", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "So what did I have an effect on ", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You know what I mea", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No what", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Why didn't you tell me", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No. you didn't!  If you really thought I could make my own decisions, you would've let me go out with him instead of helping Daddy hold me hostage", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You were paid to take me out!  By", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Really?  What was it like?  A down payment now, then a bonus for sleeping with me", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " So tell me about this dance. Was it fun", "docId": "10-Things-I-Hate-About-You.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Which parts", "qsentId": 40}]